<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Activities | Xiang Li | 李想</title>
    <link>https://idealeer.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://idealeer.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Activities</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2021-2021 Xiang Li</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://idealeer.github.io/media/icon_hua6c05f0c482061ef168fae8823b6b04c_506812_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>https://idealeer.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech of the DSN &#39;21 paper: Fast IPv6 Network Periphery Discovery and Security Implications</title>
      <link>https://idealeer.github.io/post/thu-seu-communication-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://idealeer.github.io/post/thu-seu-communication-2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We propose a novel IPv6 network periphery discovery approach. Specifically, &lt;em&gt;XMap&lt;/em&gt;, a fast network scanner, is developed to find the periphery, such as a home router. We evaluate it on twelve prominent Internet service providers and harvest &lt;em&gt;52M&lt;/em&gt; active peripheries. Grounded on these found devices, we explore IPv6 network risks of the unintended exposed security services and the flawed traffic routing strategies. First, we demonstrate the unintended exposed security services in IPv6 networks, such as DNS, and HTTP, have become emerging security risks by analyzing &lt;em&gt;4.7M&lt;/em&gt; peripheries. Second, by inspecting the periphery’s packet routing strategies, we present the flawed implementations of IPv6 routing protocol affecting &lt;em&gt;5.8M&lt;/em&gt; router devices. Attackers can exploit this common vulnerability to conduct effective routing loop attacks, inducing DoS to the ISP’s and home routers with an amplification factor of &amp;gt;&lt;em&gt;200&lt;/em&gt;. We responsibly disclose those issues to all involved vendors and ASes and discuss mitigation solutions. Our research results indicate that the security community should revisit IPv6 network strategies immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt;      Apr 17, 2021 11:40 AM &amp;ndash; 12:10 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event:&lt;/strong&gt;     THU and SEU Academic Communication Meeting on Cyberspace Security&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt;  Jiulonghu Hotel
No.77, Suyuan Avenue, Jiangning
Nanjing, Jiangsu, China&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
